hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com 2008-06-17

# Privacy / Terms and Conditions - Hollywood Toys & Costumes - Halloween Costumes - Holiday Costumes - Costume Accessories

| [  
Adults](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/adults) | [  
Kids](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/kids) | [Accessories  
& Props](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/accessories-props) | [Wigs  
& Hats](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/wigs-hats) | [  
Masks](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/masks) | [Toys  
& Collectibles ](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/toys-collectibles) | [  
My Account](http://www.hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com/mystart.php)  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| Privacy / Terms & Conditions  
---  
   
| **Privacy**  
---  
  
Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com respects the privacy concerns of the users of its internet site and has created this privacy statement to explain what information we gather from your visit to our Site and how such information may be used. 

Use of Information: As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail Address, is automatically collected from your visit to Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com’s internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience.

Our Site’s various registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact informat _ion (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail addre_ ss) demographic information _(such as your age and gend_ er). Personally identifiable information is never sold, leased or disclosed to any third parties.

Our Site uses various order forms for you to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information _(such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address)_ , and when appropriate, financial information _(your credit card number)_ to process your request or purchase. Contact information from an order form is used to fulfill orders, and to provide information about our company to you if requested. The contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding your order. Financial information that is collected is used to process your request for products, and will not be shared with third parties who are not involved with the transaction. 

**Security**

Security is a priority at Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com and we take every precaution necessary to ensure your purchasing experience with us is enjoyable as well as safe.  We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypting to ensure your personal information is kept private and secure. Credit card information is collected for purchases and transmitted via Geotrust encryption, one of the most trusted security providers on the Internet.

The use of this Site indicates your agreement to the Privacy statement above. Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com reserve the right to make changes and updates to this Privacy statement. All changes will be posted here in the Privacy / Terms & Conditions section of our website. Please check back periodically to view any such changes.   
  
**Returns**  
  
If your purchase is unsatisfactory because of size, defect, or error in shipping, you may return it within **** two (2) days **** from receipt of shipment. If it is not returned within two (2) days from your receipt of shipment, we will assume that you are satisfied with your purchase. No return will be accepted for merchandise returned after two (2) days from your receipt of shipment. ****

_Requirements for Returning Merchandise_

  1. A Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) must be obtained by email within two (2) days of your receipt of shipment, at [cs@hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com](mailto:cs@hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com). Packages will not be accepted without a Return Merchandise Authorization.  The request for an RMA must include: 
    * The reason for the return
    * The Order Number from your packing slip
    * The date of purchase

  2. All returns must be accompanied by the original packing slip enclosed with your shipment, and a separate note stating the reason for the return.
  3. All merchandise authorized to be returned must be returned to the address specified in the RMA, via a traceable shipping method, such as UPS, with delivery confirmation, and all shipping charges must be prepaid by the sender.
  4. We must receive all returns within a maximum of twelve (12) days from your receipt of shipment.
  5. We do not accept returns on the following items: 
    * Wigs, beards, facial hair or any other artificial hair
    * Fangs or any other fake teeth
    * Masks
    * Socks and stockings
    * Special order items
    * Closeout or Clearance sale items
    * Items determined in the sole discretion of Hollywoodtoysandcostumes.com to have been worn, used, damaged, altered or showing any signs of wear
    * Items not in the manufacturer’s original packaging
    * tems in damaged or torn packaging or otherwise in unsalable condition

**Refunds**  
  
If returns meet ALL of the requirements listed above, a refund may be given.

Refunds are for the cost of the merchandise ONLY and do NOT include shipping charges. Any return received with missing items or without original packaging will not be refunded. Returns are generally processed within one (1) to two (2) weeks of receipt of the return. During Halloween or holiday seasons (October through January) this process may take up to four (4) weeks.

Only your purchase price for the merchandise is refundable. Customer is responsible for all shipping charges and any additional charges incurred to return merchandise.  These shipping charges will NOT be refunded.

In our sole discretion, if a return does not meet ALL of the above requirements, we may reject the return completely, accept is partially, or accept the return with a twenty percent (20%) re-stocking and handling charge deducted from the full purchase price of the returned merchandise.

**No Halloween merchandise may be returned after October 24th.**  
**Shipping Policy**  
  
All orders received before Midnight, P.S.T. will be shipped within 24 to 48 hours pending credit card approval and inventory availability. You may receive your order in separate shipments, based on distribution point and the availability of inventory. Depending on the carrier Saturday, Sunday and holidays may be excluded as shipping days. We will immediately ship all portions of your order we have in stock. Any remaining items will be shipped as soon as they become available.

We do not ship C.O.D.  All orders must be paid using the forms of payment specified above, or available at the time of your order.

We currently ship only within the United States.  For shipping to countries other than the United States, please contact us directly with your request and we will do our best to accommodate your request for international shipments on a case by case basis  
  
**Shipping Methods**  
  
We generally ship using UPS, but may chose different carriers based on the particulars of each order or availability, chosen at our sole discretion.

We cannot guarantee an exact arrival date for your order. Our standard methods of shipment are as follows:

| Economy | Generally arrives 6 to 10 business days after shipment  
---|---  
Standard | Generally arrives 3 to 6 business days after shipment  
Express | Generally arrives 2 to 3 business days after shipment  
Premium | Generally arrives 1 o 2 business days after shipment  
  
Some costumes or items are oversized and do not fall within our normal shipping rates. Mascots, Santa suits, and oversized items require extra shipping and handling which will be quoted to you upon receipt of your order.  
  
**Shipping Charges**  
  
Our shipping charges are based on the value of the order.  Our base shipping charges for orders up to $20 are as follows:

| 

**_Economy_**

| 

**_  Standard_**

| 

**_  Express_**

| 

**_  Premium_**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
 $4.95 

| 

 $5.95 

| 

 $8.95 

| 

 $17.95   
  
Thereafter, shipping charges are increased with the increase in the value of your order.  Shipping charges are shown at the time of checkout and you have he ability to select alternative methods of shipment to meet your delivery requirement and the respective shipping charges.  
  
**Free Economy Shipping Promotion**  
For a limited time, we offer Free Economy Shipping for orders over $50.  This Free Economy Shipping offer will be automatically applied to your purchase during the checkout process.  No action needs to be taken by you in order to benefit from this offer other than to purchase over $50 in products.  The $50 purchase requirement is for the cost of product only and does not include any other charges, including shipping or taxes, if any.  

|  |   
---|---
